Kanimozhi Kalidass

Nanmangalam, Chennai

Mobile - +91 8056503717 Email - kanikrk@gmail.com

Objective

Highly-motivated employee with desire to take on new challenges. Possesses seasoned abilities with identification of operational issues and methods to address them. Having 12+ years work experience which includes various roles and responsibilities in Investment Banking, Reconciliation, Auditing and Financial statements.

Job Summary

- Senior Process Associate in TATA Consultancy Services , Chennai March 2013 to January 2023.
- Audit Assistant in M/s. Seenivasan and Balasubramaniam Associates, Kovilpatti April 2010 to February 2013.

Skills/Certification

- Investment Banking
- Financial Statements
- Income Tax filing
- MS Office
- Tally ERP

Career History

TATA Consultancy Services, Chennai

Senior Process Associate - 03/2013 - 01/2023

- As an Acting Team Lead for 13 members, handled management calls with onshore and offshore, monthly reports and managed team in a professional way.
- Prepared Reconciliation for both Cash and Bank in Private Banking Operations for the client -Morgan Stanley.
- Investigating on Missing Swifts and Out of balance Accounts and by providing the details to be in balance.
- Investigating the Breaks and report the cause of the aged breaks to the respective BU.
- Collaborated with team to define business requirements for organizational processes, meet productivity goals, and maintain accuracy standards.
- Created standard operating procedures and workflow documentation for current and future process steps. Tracked all process changes and communicated them to the team on a regular basis.

- Basic Knowledge in the areas of Corporate Actions, Derivatives, Equity and Fixed Income & Performed Macros.
- Managing Lending Control Reporting such as FRN (Floating Rate Note), Booking Sample for LAL Accounts for Domestic and International Purpose & Non-Purpose Loans, Portfolio Loan Accounts Queries, CIP (Customer Identification Program), Closed Loan and TPPA (Third Party Pledge Agreement).
- Handling Bond Analysis and Audit Reports for all types of requests such as Name and Address Change, PIN Change, Debit and Credit Card, and so on.
- Providing team members with project-specific training, establishing client requirements, and insisting on critical checkpoints to eliminate doubts.
- Applications used: Intellimatch, Loan IQ, OnDemand, 3D, RTM, Leopard, Qwest, JACADA,
 First Datanet, MS Office.

M/s. Seenivasan and Balasubrmaniam Associates | Kovilpatti.

Audit Assistant - 04/2010 - 02/2013

- Prepared Tax Calculation Statements, Financial Statements, Other Schedules, Letters and Deeds pertaining to the clients.
- Handled E-Filing and Manual Filing of Income Tax Returns for Individuals and Companies.
- Coordinated and assisted with assembly and distribution of draft and final audit reports.
- Handled all Business calls in an effective manner as a PRO as well
- Handled Bank Audit and College Audit. Adhered to departmental controls and regulations, maintaining ethical conduct at all times.
- Create and interpret reports detailing the progress and findings of audits in order to share with managerial staff.
- Proof all claims that are made by verifying totals, calculations and general accounts submitted throughout audit.

Professional/Personal Achievements

- Successfully implemented Performing of manual reconciliations into Intellimatch Application
 Automation for the Daily Workflow, results in Cost savings.
- Awarded Best Performer by the Business Development Team

Key Skills

- Quick Learner, Able to work under pressure.
- Problem Solving and Communication
- Excellent in Team management, Time management & Multitasking

Educational Qualification

B.Com., in G.Venkataswamy Naidu College, Kovilpatti, Tamilnadu (2007-2010)